A Collection of Scrapbooks LSC.0155
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Scrapbook no. 80: Errinerungen an Meiningen und Herzog Georg II, 1 v.; 35 cm (Box 78)
  Photographs and newspaper clippings about the town of Meiningen, Germany, Duke Georg II von Sachsen-Meiningen and the theater. From the Altman collection
- Scrapbook no. 81: Cigar labels album, Ca. 1910; 1 v.; 33 cm (Box 107)
- Scrapbook no. 82: English buildings and scenery of the 18th and 19th centuries, 1 v.; 38 cm (Box 43)
- Scrapbook no. 83: Shakespeare scrapbook, Ca. 1900 - 1930; 1 v.; 37 cm (Box 105)
  Newspaper clippings concerning Shakespeare's plays, and the Shakespeare-Bacon controversy. Includes some Player's cigarette cards with various Shakespearean scenes
- Scrapbook no. 84: Ferguson, Lillian (Prest), - 1955, Ca. 1923 - 1955; 2 vols. (Box 72)
  Scrapbooks, Laguna Beach, Cal. Mrs. Ferguson was a Southern California painter and potter
- Scrapbook no. 86: Pinger, Wilhelm Robert Richard, 1873 - 1917, 1914; 1 v.; 36 cm (Box 115)
  Scrapbook of a trip to Germany. [Compiled in Berkeley, Cal?]
- Scrapbook no. 87: Palmer, William T., 1937 - 1938; 1 v.; 35 cm (Box 44)
  Scrapbook of the autor's newpapers columns [England]
- Scrapbook no. 88: Cigar labels and advertising cards album, Ca. 1887; 1 v. 32 cm (Box 44)
- Scrapbook no. 89: Fernon, Thomas S., collector, 1877; 1 v.; 32 cm (Box 102)
  Railroad riots, Philadelphia, summer of 1877
- Scrapbook no. 90 vols. 2-3: Humphries, Sydney, 1862 - 1941, 1898 - 1910 (Box 45)
  Volumes are bound by Douglas B. Cockerell
- Scrapbook no. 90 vol. 1: Humphries, Sydney, 1861 - 1941, 1898 - 1910 (Box 64)
  Vol. 1 contains review clippings of the author's "Carpets, carpers and critics" (London, Black, 1910). Volumes are bound by Douglas B> Cockerell
- Scrapbook no. 91: Southern California scrapbook, Ca. 1910 - 1928; 1 v.; 31 cm (Box 26)
- Scrapbook no. 92: Victorian scrapbook, Ca. 1860 - 1880; 1 v.; 30 cm (Box 26)
  Includes examples of punched and gilded paper borders, Valentines, and flower paintings
- Scrapbook no. 93: Glover, May E., 1937 - 1938; 1 v.; 28 cm (Box 53)
  Mrs. Glover was an active member of the Order of the Eastern Star in Arcadia, California.
- Scrapbook no. 94: Advertising cards album, Ca. 1890; 1 v.; 29 cm (Box 53)
- Scrapbook no. 95: Kern County scrapbook, 1938; 1 v. unbound; 30 cm (Box 53)
  Photographs of Kern County and California along US highway 99
- Scrapbook no. 96: Hood, Irene J., "The pictured story of our California trip...", 1903; 1 v.; 29 cm (Box 53)
  Colorado Springs, Colo., contains photographs and illustrations
- Scrapbook no. 97: Pencil sketches of European scenes and fashions, 1867 - 1901; 1 v.; 29 cm (Box 54)
- Scrapbook no. 98: Trading and advertising cards album, Ca. 1880 - 1890; 1 v.; 28 cm (Box 54)
- Scrapbook no. 99: Letter and account book., 1 v.; 28 cm (Box 54)
  Manufactured by Thornton and Pattison, Hull, England. A fine specimen af an unused letter book
- Scrapbook no. 100 box 1: Dickson, Edward Augustus, 1879 - 1956. Newspaper clippings scrapbooks, Ca. 1900 - 1940; 4 boxes (Box 46)
  Box 1: Early days in Los Angeles; 1940 new events; 1931 political file
- Scrapbook no. 100 box 2: Dickson, Edward Augustus, 1879 - 1956. Newspaper clipping scrapbooks, Ca. 1900 - 1940; 4 boxes (Box 47)
  Box 2: Germany, ca. 1912 - 1934
- Scrapbook no. 100 box 3: Dickson, Edward Augustus, 1879 - 1956. Newspaper clipping scrapbooks, Ca. 1900 - 1949; 4 boxes (Box 48)
  Box 3: New York campaign 1905-6; Arizona and New Mexico statehood problems; Old time Doings; San Francisco ,ayoralty elections 1903
- Scrapbook no. 100 box 4: Dickson, Edward Augustus, 1899 - 1983. Newspaper clipping scrapbooks, Ca. 1900 - 1940; 4 boxes (Box 49)
  Box 4: Europe and the Russo-Japanese war, 1900 - 1910
- Scrapbook no. 101: Von Schmidt, Harold. The forty-niners, calendar illustrations, 1949; 1 v.; 29 cm (Box 50)
- Scrapbook no. 102: Obituary notices concerning Lord O'Brien, 1914; 1 v.; 25 cm (Box 50)
- Scrapbook no. 103: English portrait and facsimile autographs of the 17th century, 1 v.; 23 cm (Box 50)
- Scrapbook no. 104: Molnar, Ferenc, 1878 - 1952. Reviews of "Liliom," New York: Boni & Liveright, 1921 (Box 50)
  Includes newpaper reviews of both the book, and stage performances
- Scrapbook no. 105: Theater programs scrapbook, 1872 - 1934; 4 v.; 27 cm (Box 51)
  A collection made by Helen Broderick Crawford consisting chiefly of casts of plays excerpted from New York and Paris theater programs of the early 20th century, but including a few late 19th century
- Scrapbook no. 106: Victorian scrapbook, 1887; 1 v; 37 cm (Box 84)
  A collection of embossed and chromolitho-graphed punch-scrap depicting flowers, fruits, animals, people, views, and three adaptations of children's stories: Puss in boots, Robinson Crusoe, and Cock Robin. With embossed copper cover
- Scrapbook no. 107: Fax, Reuben, Ca. 1896; 1 v.; 29 cm (Box 52)
  Scrapbook containing newspaper clippings, theater programs, letters and pictures relating to the Australian production of "Trilby" with Mr. Fax in the role of Svengali
- Scrapbook no. 108: Beecher, Henry Ward, 1813 - 1887, Ca. 1887; 1 v.; 30 cm (Box 52)
  Scrapbook of newspaper clippings relating to the final illness and death of Henry Ward Beecher, with eulogies, memorials, etc.
- Scrapbook no. 109: Castles, Alfred Guido, 1851 -, Ca. 1920 - 1935; 2 v.; 29 x 38 cm (Box 80)
  Newspapers clippings relating chiefly to Charles Lindbergh. Also clippings concerning Dr. and Mrs. Castles & their entertaining and guests at Castle Sans Souci in Holllywood. Dr. Castles translated his name from Schloesser to affirm his patriotism
- Scrapbook no. 110:, n.d.; 1 v. (Box 81)
  Scrapbook containing clippings, letters, photographs, and art work by or relating to Mrs. Starene H. Swineford, California born and educated art teacher
- Scrapbook no. 111: Children's storybook scrapbook, Ca. 1868; 1 v.; 37 cm (Box 107)
  Illustrated story books for young children, cut out and mountedm most without title pages. Contents: ABC, Baby's birthday and how it was spent, Chattering Jack, Little Bo-Peep, Little Red Riding Hood paper doll, Old Mother Hubbard, and others
- Scrapbook no. 112: Muir, John, 1838 - 1914, 1 v.; 29 cm (Box 102)
  Contains periodical publications by John Muir, articles about John Muir, and check lists of some of his works. Gift of William A. Carr
- Scrapbook no. 113: Milliron, Clark J., 1883 -, collector, 1930; 1 v. (Box 89)
  A scrapbook of photographs and ephemera relating to a visit to Los Angeles on August 25, 1930 of W. Cameron Forbes, Governor General of the Philippines, newly appointed ambasador to Japan
- Scrapbook no. 114: Scrapbook concerning Edward VII, King of Great Britain, 1841 - 1910, 1 vol. (Box 98)
- Scrapbook no. 115:, 1898; 1 v.; 14 in. (Box 80)
  A scrapbook of newspapers clippings collected in Germany revealing anti-American bias during the Spanish-American War
- Scrapbook no. 116: Plates to Gay's Fables (Box 25)
  Unsigned etchings mounted one to a leaf. The edition they illustrate has not been identified. Ex-libris C.K. Ogden
- Scrapbook no. 117: Robinson, John Henry, 1796 - 1871. Scrapbook of engravings, original drawings, and water colors, 19th cent.; 1 v.; 37 x 48 cm (Box 79)
  A collection of the work of J.H. Robinson, R.A., probably assembled by one of his children, consisting of more than 150 items, including many original sketches and water colors, engraved title pages and illustrations for books
- Scrapbook no. 118: Hatfield, Charles M., Ca. 1906 - 1963; 2 reels (Box Unknown container 1498 for instance of Scrapbook no. 118: Hatfield, Charles M.)
  Positive microfilm of scrapbooks about the rainmaking efforts of Charles M. Hatfield, incl. clippings about Paul Hatfield's rainmaking efforts after his brother's death. The originals are in the Los Angeles Public Library. Not found 10/90
- Scrapbook no. 119: Eaton, Seymore, 1859 - 1916. The Call's home study circle, 1899 - 1900; 1 v.; 30 x 26 cm (Box 44)
  Clippings from the San Francisco Call. Home study courses include: Shakespeare, the world's great artists, desk studies for girls, great American statesmen, home science and household economy, American political parite, French conversation and more
- Scrapbook no. 120 part 2: Conlan, Charles T., 1893 - 1895; 27 x 45 cm (Box 81)
  Newspaper clippings concerning the cases of reform judge Charles T. Conlan. One scrapbook is devoted entirely to the sensational murders of Blanch Lamont and Marian Williams by Theodore Durant. San Francisco
- Scrapbook no. 120 parts 1 & 3: Conlan, Charles T., 1893 - 1895; 27 x 45 cm (Box 90)
  Newspaper clippings concerning the cases of reform judge Charles T. Conlan. One scrapbook is devoted entirely to the sensational murders of Blanche Lamont and Marian Williams by Theodore Durant. Sna Francisco
- Scrapbook no. 121: American humor and humorists scrapbook, Ca. 1880 - 1938; 1 v.; 31 cm (Box 75)
  Included is an envelope of unmounted clippings. The album is paginated and indexed. Gifto of Walt Disney Studios
- Scrapbook no. 122: Real Estate business scrapbook, Los Angeles, 1907 - 1915; 142 items; *** (Box Unknown container 1499 for instance of Scrapbook no. 122: Real Estate business scrapbook, Los Angeles)
  Tract maps, holdings maps, price lists and promotionsl materila relating to Los Anglels and vicinity. There is an index in the scrapbook collection folder. All items are individually encapsulated in mylar. Triple oversize - shelved in map room
- Scrapbook no. 123 vol. 1: Theater scrapbooks, 1907 - 1917; 3 vols.; 60 cm (Box 95)
  Newspaper clippings regarding plays and performers appearing in Los Angeles. Gift of John F. Huber
- Scrapbook no. 123 vol. 1: Theater scrapbooks, 1907 - 1917; 3 vols.; 60 cm (Box 97)
  Newpapers clippings regarding plays and performers appearing in Los Angeles. Gift of John F. Huber
- Scrapbook no. 123 vol. 2: Theater scrapbooks, 1907 - 1917; 3 vols.; 60 cm (Box 96)
  Newspapers clippings regarding plays and performers appearing in Los Angeles. Gift of John F. Huber
- Scrapbook no. 124 vols. 1 & 2: French historical postcard series, 5 vols.; 25 x 32 cm (Box 27)
  Vols. 1 & 2: series on views of ancient Paris and Lyons, decorative arts and sculpture. Much of the material is chiefly illustrative of the 18th and 19th centuries. Ex libris Charles Boyer
- Scrapbook no. 124 vols. 3 & 4: French historical postcard series, 5 vols.; 25 x 32 (Box 28)
  Vols. 3 & 4: Series on costumes, uniforms, manners and customs, etc. Much of the material is chiefly illustrative of the 18th and 19th centuries. Ex libris Charles Boyer
- Scrapbook no. 124 vol. 5: French historical postcard series, 5 vols.; 25 x 32 (Box 29)
  Vol. 5: Series on French cities, interiors, landscapes, monuments and costume. Much of the material is chiefly illustrative of the 18th and 19th centuries. Ex libris: Charles Boyer
- Scrapbook no. 125: French scrapbook, 1813 - 1951; 1 vol.; 30 - 27 cm (Box 114)
  A collection of ephemera relating to transportation, business, public administration, restaurants and theaters, including bus tickets, menus, programs, pamphlets, permits, and two wills dated 1813. Ex libris Charles Boyer
- Scrapbook no. 127: Theater scrapbook, Ca. 1890; 1 v. (Box 62)
  Pictures of actors and actresses and scenes from plays taken from jounals and newspapers. Disbound
- Scrapbook no. 128: Political scrapbook, 1898 - 1899; 1 v.; 35 x 26 (Box 81)
  Newspaper clippings relating to the unsuccessful campaign for U.S. Senate of California State Senator Robert N. Bulla
- Scrapbook no. 129, v.1: World War II, 1939 - 1945; 42 x 37 cm (Box 82)
  Ex libris Gloria Stuart Sheekman
- Scrapbook no. 129, v.2: World War II, 1939 - 1945; 42 x 37 cm (Box 87)
- Scrapbook no. 129, v.3: World War II, 1939 - 1945; 35 x 30 (Box 83)
- Scrapbook no. 130: Feature article newspaper scrapbook, Ca. 1900; 1 vol.; 45 x 30 cm (Box 88)
  Newspapers clippings relating to foreign lands or strange peoples. Many are columns by Frank George Carpenter. Includes popular pieces about indians of the Southwest and interesting or unusual places in California
- Scrapbook no. 131: Miscellaneous scrapbook, 1874 - 1892; 1 vol.; 23 x 18 (Box 62)
  Includes an article about the San Francisco Telegraph and Telephone Company and the Fire Patrol as reported in the Daily Post (London?), June 11, 1878. Ex libris C.K. Ogden
- Scrapbook no. 132: McCarthy era scrapbooks, 1948 - 1953; 2 vols.; 29 cm (Box 30)
  Newspaper clippings mounted in loose leaf binders. One volume emphasizes anti-semitism and anti- communism abroad; the other relates mostly to the United States with a section of clippings on the Hollywood Ten
- Scrapbook no. 133: Buxton scrapbook, 1927 - 1941; 1 vol.; 30 x 25.5 cm (Box 30)
  Newspapers clippings relating chiefly to Buxton (England), its cricket team, and athletic events of various kinds. It also includes clippings about the history of the town
- Scrapbook no. 134: Carlyle scrapbook (England), 1 vol.; 16 x 11 cm (Box 62)
  Carlyle's "On the choice of books," London, Hotten, n.d. used as a scrapbook for material relating to Thomas Carlyle. Gift of John Harmon, 1976
- Scrapbook no. 135: Davenport, Homer Calvin, 1867 - 1912, Ca. 1900; 1 vol.; 41 x 30 cm (Box 84)
  Newspapers reproductions of Davenport cartoons mounted in a copy of Homer C. Davenport's "Cartoons," New York, 1898
- Scrapbook no. 136: Celebrity scrapbooks (England), Ca. 1900; 2 vols.; 36 cm (Box 89)
  Magazine pictures of royalty, nobility, theatrical celebrities, and animals, interspersed with watercolor drawings and humorous commentary. Vol. 1 missing 5/91
- Scrapbook no. 137: Spanish lithographic views (Cadiz and Paris), 19th c.; 1 vol.; 38 x 55 cm (Box 106)
  12 lithographs and one engraving mounted on stubs showing 19th century views of Cadiz and Seville, the work of various artists
- Scrapbook no. 138: Whitsell, Grace Anna, 1890 - 1924; 1 vol.; 15 x 34 cm (Box 31)
  Grace Whitsell was a Los Angeles lyric soprano who sang at church concerts and for the Santa Fe Railroad Co. Her scrapbook contains programs of her concerts, mostly in Southern Calif, newspaper clippings, and dance programs. Gift of Peggy Christian
- Scrapbook no. 139: Beverly Hills building permits scrapbook, 1923 - 1926; 1 item; 28 cm (Box 62)
  Clippings of building permit lists qublished weekly giving name, address, type and cost of construction
- Scrapbook no. 140: Young, Arthur Henry, 1866 - 1943, Ca. 1920s; 1 item; 41 cm (Box 84)
  Political and humorous cartoons from newspapers and magazines by Art Young. Portfolio scrapbook.
- Scrapbook no. 141 vol.1: Southern Pacific Lines menu collection, 1933 - 1947; 7 vols.; 33 cm (Box 32)
  Special occasion menus for club tours, football game trains, and similar charters. Approximately 1500 items. Vol. 1. Feb 1933 - Aug. 1934.
- Scrapbook no. 141 vol.2: Southern Pacific Lines menu collection, 1933 - 1947; 7 vols.; 33 cm (Box 33)
  Special occasion menus for club tours, football game trains, and similar charters. Approximately 1500 items. Vol. 2. Oct. 1934 - Jun. 1935.
- Scrapbook no. 141 vol.3: Southern Pacific Lines menu collection, 1933 - 1947; 7 vols.; 33 cm (Box 34)
  Special occasion menus for club tours, football game trains, and similar charters. Approximately 1500 items. Vol. 3. Jun. 1935 - Jan. 1936.
- Scrapbook no. 141 vol.4: Southern Pacific Lines menu collection, 1933 - 1947; 7 vols.; 33 cm (Box 35)
  Special occasion menus for club tours, football game trains, and similar charters. Approximately 1500 items. Vol. 4. Jan. 1936 - Sep. 1936
- Scrapbook no. 141 vol.5: Southern Pacific Lines menu collection, 1933 - 1947; 7 vols.; 33 cm (Box 36)
  Special occasion menus for club tours, football game trains, and similar charters. Approximately 1500 items. Vol. 5. Oct. 1936 - Feb. 1937
- Scrapbook no. 141 vol.6: Southern Pacific Lines menu collection, 1933 - 1947; 7 vols.; 33 cm (Box 37)
  Special occasion menus for club tours, football game trains, and similar charters. Approximately 1500 items. Vol. 6. April 1937 - Oct. 1937.
- Scrapbook no. 141 vol.7: Southern Pacific Lines menu collection, 1933 - 1947; 7 vols.; 33 cm (Box 38)
  Special occasion menus for club tours, football game trains, and similar charters. Approximately 1500 items. Vol. 7. May 1946 - Jun. 1947.
- Scrapbook no. 142: Lithographs from La Caricature (Paris) (Box 21)
  An almost complete collection of caricatures from La Caricature, journal fonde et dirige par C Philipon, manu of them by Grandville. Bound in morocco-backed marbled boards. Ex-libris Charles Boyer
- Scrapbook no. 143: Partello Stock Company, 1906 - 1915; 80 p.; 30 x 18.5 cm (Box 38)
  Includes photographs and newspaper clippings relating mostly to the Partello players, some of whom were black. There are a few clippings relating to other stock companies.
- Scrapbook no. 144 v. 1-4: Theater scrapbooks, 1888 - 1938; 8 vols. (Box 56)
  Apparently kept by 2 people: 1888 - 1907 by W.L. Hobart; 1903 - 1938 by F.M. Bischoff. They contain programs, clippings, reviews from New York & Los Angeles & notes incl. dates of attendance. Ex-libris Ralph Freud
- Scrapbook no. 144 v. 5-8: Theater scrapbooks, 1888 - 1939; 8 vols. (Box 57)
- Scrapbook no. 145: Gale, Edmund Walter, 1884 -. Cartoon scrapbook, Ca. 1908; 1 vol.; 24.5 x 20 cm (Box 31)
  Consists mostly of cartoons by Gale, originally published in the LOs Angeles Examiner, together with miscellaneous newpaper clippings. Gift of Arnold Rubin, 1977
- Scrapbook no. 146: Woodcut illustrations from early printed books, n.d.; 36 l.; 36 x 29 cm (Box 74)
  Mounted clippings of woodcuts assembled from what appears to be twentieth century magazine publecations. Unbound.
- Scrapbook no. 147: Ando, Hiroshige, 1797 - 1858. The fifty-three stations of Tokaido, Ca. 1910; 55 pieces; 9 x 14 cm (Box 57)
  The pricession march of Minister Ryu-Kyu showing the 53 lodging stations plus the start and finish. Reduced from the original Hiroshige Hoeido edition, 1833. Wood block print postcards
- Scrapbook no. 148: Entertainment notices, Ca. 1880s; 93 items (Box 39)
  Includes miniature playbills with color lithograph scenes or portraits relating to the plays, very much like trade cards. Assembled in plastic protector sleeves
- Scrapbook no. 149: Victorian scrapbook, Ca. 1881; 1 vol.; 21.5 x 17.5 cm (Box 39)
  A collection of chromolithographed punch-scrap and cards depicting fruits, flowers and animals
- Scrapbook no. 150: The Philippines, 1898 - 1902; 3 vols.; 38 cm (Box 86)
  Newspaper clippings relating to the Philippines. Vol. 1: August 1898 - October 1899; vol. 2: October 1899 - August 1900; vol. 3: August 1900 - January 1902. Index in each volume. [Another copy: 1 reel 35mm microfilm]
- Scrapbook no. 151: John Joseph Cantwell, D.D., first Archbishop of Los Angeles, 1947; 55 l.; 36 cm. (Box 65)
  Newspapers articles and obituaries assembled from newspapers at the time of Archbishop Cantwell's death. Gift of Peggy Christian
- Scrapbook no. 152: Postcard views of California, 2 vols. (Box 165)
  Approximately 300 postcards. Vol. 1: Southern California; vol. 2: Northern California
- Scrapbook no. 153: Italy. Postcard scrapbook, Ca. 1920; 1 vol.; 34 cm. (Box 69)
- Scrapbook no. 154: France. Postcard scrapbook, Ca. 1920; 1 vol.; 34 cm. (Box 68)
- Scrapbook no. 155: Switzerland. Postcard scrapbook, Ca. 1920; 1 vol.; 34 cm. (Box 66)
- Scrapbook no. 155: Spain. Postcard scrapbook, Ca. 1920; 1 vol.; 34 cm. (Box 66)
- Scrapbook no. 156: Holland, Belgium, Germany, Austria and Bohemia. Postcard scrapbook, Ca. 1920; 1 vol.; 34 cm. (Box 67)
- Scrapbook no. 158: Egypt. Postcard scrapbook, Ca. 1920; 1 vol.; 34 cm. (Box 91)
  Included are some views of the U.S., of England and of Greece
- Scrapbook no. 159: Engravings scrapbook., Ca. 1810s; 1 vol.; 19 x 15 cm. (Box 31)
  Approximately 400 engravings depicting castles, estates and scenery, chiefly in Great Britain. Bound in maroon straight grain morocco. Ex-libris: C.K. Ogden
- Scrapbook no. 160: Victorian scrap albums compiled by Jemima and Chrissy Grigg., 1856 - 1871t; 2 vols.; 20 cm. (Box 31)
  Verses and drawings by friends of the compilers. Book I incl. materials by and about John Williams Hipango (Hoani Wiremu) of Wanganui, New Zealand, a Maori Chief who visited the Griggs. Also verses illuminated by Charlotte E. Emra, 1858
- Scrapbook no. 161: Victorian scrapbook belonging to Ulrich Steindorff, 1880s; 1 vol.; 30.8 cm. (Box 56)
  Collection of chromolithographed punchscrap depicting anthropomorphic anumals, flowers, famous people, etc
- Scrapbook no. 162: McCutcheon, George Barr, 1866 - 1928. Scrapbook relating to Graustark, 1901 - 1902; 56 l.; 32 cm. (Box Unknown container 1500 for instance of Scrapbook no. 162: McCutcheon, George Barr, 1866 - 1928. Scrapbook relating to Graustark)
  McCutcheon's collection of newpaper clippings of advertising and reviews relating to his novel, including his holograph table of contents. [Not found 10/91]
- Scrapbook no. 163: Los Angeles theater programs, Ca. 1903 - 1907 (Box 85)
- Scrapbook no. 164, vols. 1-3: Clippings and photographs of movie stars, Ca. 1939; 6 vols. (Box 129)
- Scrapbook no. 164, vols. 4-6: Clippings and photographs of movie stars, Ca. 1939; 6 vols. (Box 130)
- Scrapbook no. 165, vol. 1: Clippings of stage and screen stars, Ca. 1914 - 1924; 3 vols. (Box 131)
  Includes index
- Scrapbook no. 165, vol. 2: Clippings of stage and screen stars, Ca. 1914 - 1924; 3 vols. (Box 132)
- Scrapbook no. 165, vol. 3: Clippings of stage and screen stars, Ca. 1914 - 1924; 3 vols. (Box 133)
- Scrapbook no. 165 vols. 1-2: Theater scrapbook, Ca. 1903 - 1906; 2 vols. (Box 134)
  Includes index. Ex libris Grace E. Runyan-Wilkinson (1883 - 1955). Gift of Albert J. Wilkinson.
- Scrapbook no. 166: Sketches, watercolors, poems and clippings, Ca. 1830 - 1860; 1 vol. (Box 134)
- Scrapbook no. 167: Sketch and watercolor book, 1878; 1 vol (Box 135)
  Ex-libris Emma Liliace Graham
- Scrapbook no. 168: Book of the Coronation, 1953; 1 vol. (Box 135)
  With clippings about the coronation
- Scrapbook no. 169: Fascism in America, Utopians, Silver Shirts, Other Organizations, Civil Liberties & anti- communism, Ca. 1934; 1 vol. (Box 135)
  Clippings, mainly from Los Angeles
- Scrapbook no. 170: Scrapbook about Ralph Waldo Emerson, Ca. 1822 - 1903; 1 vol. (Box 135)
  Ex-libris John Quinn
- Scrapbook no. 171: "My memory book" by Catherine Briggs, Los Angeles, 1916 - 1917; 1 vol. (Box 135)
- Scrapbook no. 172, vols. 1-2: Clippings of stage and screen stars with indexes, Ca 1916 - 1932; 4 vols. (Box 136)
- Scrapbook no. 172, vols. 3-4: Clippings of stage and screen stars with indexes, Ca. 1916 - 1932; 4 vols. (Box 137)
- Scrapbook no. 173: Victorian scrapbook of postcards and chromolithographed punch scrap, Ca 1880s; 1 vol. (Box 138)
- Scrapbook no. 174: Victorian scrapbook of greeting cards and chromolithographed punch scrap, Ca. 1880s; 1 vol. (Box 138)
- Scrapbook no. 175: Victorian scrapbook of poems and colored illustrations of flowers, Ca. 1880s; 1 vol. (Box 138)
- Scrapbook no. 176, vol. 1: Screen Actors Guild scrapbooks, 1946 - 1947; 2 vols. (Box 139)
- Scrapbook no. 176, vol. 2: Screen Actors Guild scrapbooks, 1946 - 1947; 2 vols. (Box 140)
- Scrapbook no. 177 vols. 1-7: British royal family, Ca. 1928 - 1946; 7 vols. (Box 141)
- Scrapbook no. 178: Mander, Raymond, "Ricordi di Italia", Early 1900s; 1 vol. (Box 142)
  Photographs of Italy
- Scrapbook no. 179, vols. 1-2: Post cards and photographs of Europe., Ca. 1929; 4 vols. (Box 143)
  Vol. 1: Great Britain, Italy, Germany, Holland, France; vol. 2: Great Britain
- Scrapbook no. 179, vols. 3-4: Post cards and photographs of Europe, Ca. 1929; 4 vols. (Box 144)
  Vol. 3: France, Canterbury, London; vol. 4: Norway, Sweden, Czechosovakia, Austria, Hungary, Yugoslavia, Italy, Gibraltar, Algeria, Portugal
- Scrapbook no. 18 vol. 10: McClurkin, James Robert, 1910 -. Scrapbooks re: World War II, 1941 - 1945; 13 volumes (Box 85)